Guide to the New Yorkers at Work Oral History Collection OH.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Celia Orlansky, Apr 30, 1981; Sep 23, 1981 (Cassette 93A - 93C, Cd OH-01-452 / OH-01-453)
- Francis Owens, undated (Cd OH-01-137, Cassette 203A)
- Rita Palter, Jan 17, 1991 (Cd OH-01-384 / OH-01-385, Cassette 170A - 170B)
- Elaine Paul, Jul 19, 1996; Jul 22, 1996 (Cassette 155A - 155C)
- Solly Pernick, Jun 16, 1986 (Cd OH-01-138 / OH-01-139 / OH-01-140 / OH-01-141, Cassette 94A MISSING)
- Beatrice Pflaster, Jun 5, 1997 (Cassette 241A - 241B, Cd OH-01-142 / OH-01-143)
- Juan Pons & Carlos Rivera, Jun 23, 1981 (Cd OH-01-363 / OH-01-364, Cassette 98A)
- Harold Pryor, Mar 16, 1989 (Cassette 211A - 211C)
- Clarence Reed, Apr 27, 1986 (Cd OH-01-226 / OH-01-227 / OH-01-228, Cassette 95A - 95C)
- William Reiter, May 29, 1986 (Cd OH-01-144, Cassette 97A)
- Elliot Rief, Mar 11, 1987 (Cd OH-01-454 / OH-01-455 / OH-01-456 / OH-01-457, Cassette 96A - 96D)
  AFSCME, District Council 37
- Carlos Rivera and Juan Pons, Jun 23, 1981 (Cassette 98A, Cassette OH-01-363 / OH-01-364)
- Charles Rivers, Apr 29, 1991 (Cassette 190A - 190D, Cd OH-01-229 / OH-01-230 / OH-01-231 / OH-01-232)
- Al Robbins, Jun 30, 1980 (Cassette 99A - 99C, Cd OH-01-145 / OH-01-146 / OH-01-147)
- Lillian Roberts, Oct 27, 1981 (Cassette 100A, Cd OH-01-395 / OH-01-396 / OH-01-397 / OH-01-398 / OH-01-399)
- Sam Robert, Jan 12, 1990 (Cassette 159A - 159B, Cd OH-01-365 / OH-01-366)
- Camille Robinson-Gardner, Jan 26, 1981 (Cassette 101A, Cd OH-01-311 / OH-01-312)
  Partial available; Transcript available Box 4; Release form Yes
- Cleveland Robinson, Oct 21, 1980; Oct 28, 1980 (Cassette 102A - 102C, Cd OH-01-308 / OH-01-309 / OH-01-310)
- Edgar Romney, Apr 1, 2003 (Cd OH-01-152, Cassette 260A)
- Abe Rosen, Apr 21, 1980 (Cassette 103A)
- Michael Rosen, Jul 20, 1979 (Cassette 104A - 104B, Cd OH-01-153 / OH-01-154)
- Morris Rosenszweig, Jun 29, 1980 (Cassette 105A - 105B, Cd OH-01-313 / OH-01-314 / OH-01-315 / OH-01-316)
- William Ross, Mar 23, 1981 (Cd OH-01-458 / OH-01-459, Cassette 106A - 106B)
- Betty Bentz Rubin & Jay Rubin, Sep 6, 1988 (Box 1, Item Session: 155)
- Paul Rubin, undated (Cassette 204A, Cd OH-01-317)
- Ernie Rymer, Jul 19, 1984 (Cassette 107A - 107B, Cd OH-01-155 / OH-01-156)
- George Schuck, undated
- Miriam (and Max) Schwadron, Apr 30, 1986 (Cd OH-01-170 / OH-01-171, Cassette 108A - 108C)
- Bea Schwartz, May 7, 1980; May 17, 1980 (Cd OH-01-157 / OH-01-158, Cassette 109A - 109B)
- George Schwartz, Jul 17, 1981 (Cd OH-01-348 / OH-01-349, Cassette 110A - 110B)
  Transcript available Box 5; Index available
- Thomas Scotland, Jun 3, 1997 (Cd OH-01-159 / OH-01-160, Cassette 242A - 242B)
  Transcript available Box 5; Index available; Release form Yes
- Martin Segal, Mar 3, 1994 (Cassette 226A)
- Ted Schapiro, Jun 11, 1998 (Cassette 254A - 254B)
- Doris Shaffer, May 27, 1991 (Cassette 205A - 205C)
- John Sheehan, Oct 19, 1990 (Cassette 178A)
- William Shelley, Apr 30, 1997 (Cd OH-01-161 / OH-01-162, Cassette 243A - 243B)
- Ken Sherbell, Jun 25, 1980; Dec 12, 1981 (Cd OH-01-163 / OH-01-164 / OH-01-165, Cassette 111A - 111B)
- Rebecca Simonson, Oct 29, 1980; Nov 10, 1980 (Cd OH-01-420 / OH-01-421 / OH-01-422 / OH-01-423 / OH-01-424, Cassette 112A - 112C)
- Shirley Simonson, Nov 19 (Cd OH-01-425, Cassette 208A)
- Lee Singer & Doris Emanuel, Oct 6, 1980 (Cd OH-01-166 / OH-01-167, Cassette 113A)
- Randall B. Smith, Nov 5, 1980; Dec 1, 1980 (Cd OH-01-318 / OH-01-319, Cassette 114A)
- Stanley Smith, Jul 16, 1981 (Cassette 115A, Cd OH-01-168 / OH-01-169)
- Lily Sokolofsky, Apr 21, 1980 (Cassette 116A, Cd OH-01-320)
- Jackie Stack, Jun 11, 1981 (Cassette 185A, Cd OH-01-321)
- Joe Stack, Nov 5, 1981 (Cassette 118A - 118C, Cd OH-01-323 / OH-01-324 / OH-01-325 / OH-01-326 / OH-01-327 / OH-01-328)
- Monroe & Matilda Stein, Feb 11, 1979 (Cd OH-01-487 / OH-01-488, Cassette 117A - 117B, Cd OH-01-481 / OH-01-482)
- Leon Sverdlove, Oct 23, 1979 (Cassette 120A - 120C, Cd OH-01-329 / OH-01-330 / OH-01-331 / OH-01-332 / OH-01-333 / OH-01-334)
  Transcript available Box 5; Release form
- Loretta Szeliga, Sep 11, 1981 (Cd OH-01-335 / OH-01-336 / OH-01-337 / OH-01-338 / OH-01-339 / OH-01-340, Cassette 119A - 119C)
- Hyman Teitelbaun, May 12, 1982 (Cd OH-01-172 / OH-01-173 / OH-01-174 / OH-01-175, Cassette 122A - 122B)
- David Tolan, Sep 1, 1980 (Cd OH-01-343 / OH-01-344, Cassette 123A)
  Transcript available Box 5
- Ida Torres, Jun 24, 1980 (Cassette 124A, Cd OH-01-176 / OH-01-177)
- Merry Tucker, Aug 2, 1981; cuid14388 (Cassette MISSING 125A)
- Merry Tucker, Aug 2, 1981; cuid14389 (Cassette 125B)
- Merry Tucker, Aug 2, 1981; cuid14390 (Cassette 125C)
- Allan Tumolillo, Jul 11, 1980 (Cassette 126A, Cd OH-01-178 / OH-01-179)
- Helen Turner, Jul 22, 1980 (Cd OH-01-341 / OH-01-342, Cassette 128A - 128B)
- United Store Workers, Local 3, Oct 16, 1979 (Cassette 130A, Cd OH-01-180 / OH-01-181)
- UPI, Local 107, undated (Cassette 129A)
- Evelyn Virgo & Anna Rouse, Jul 23, 1981 (Cd OH-01-149 / OH-01-150 / OH-01-151, Cassette 131A - 131B)
- Caesar Viruet, May 28, 1997 (Cassette 244A - 244B, Cd OH-01-460 / OH-01-461)
- Judith Vladeck, Oct 15, 2004 (Cd OH-01-476, Cassette 262A - 262D)
  Scope and Content Note
  Interview by Roger Horowitz.
- Emagene Walker, Nov 27, 1981 (Cassette 132A, Cd OH-01-182)
  Release form Yes*amended
- Pearl Walker, Dec 11, 1990 (Cd OH-01-462, Cassette 207A)
- Richard Walsh, Nov 4, 1987 (Cassette 149A - 149B, Cd OH-01-496 / OH-01-497)
- Keri Webster, Apr 17, 1991 (Cassette 206A)
- Philip Weightman, Apr 11, 1981 (Cassette 133A - 133C, Cd OH-01-345 / OH-01-346 / OH-01-347)
  AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education; Voting rights for African-Americans
- Grace Weiner, Aug 21, 1981 (Cd OH-01-183, Cassette 136A)
- Louis Weinstock, Dec 16, 1980 (Cd OH-01-184 / OH-01-185 / OH-01-186, Cassette 135A - 135B)
- Everett Wiltshire, Nov 12, 1996 (Cassette 245A - 245B, Cd OH-01-187 / OH-01-188)
- Conrad Woelfel, Mar 27, 1980 (Cassette 134A - 134B, Cd OH-01-189 / OH-01-190)
- Ruth Young, Aug 29, 1985 (Cd OH-01-463 / OH-01-464, Cassette 217A - 217B)
  Transcript available box 5
- Vincent Young, Aug 4, 1983 (Cassette 148A)
- Sol Zalon, May 29, 1980 (Cassette 139A - 139C, Cd OH-01-387 / OH-01-388 / OH-01-389 / OH-01-390 / OH-01-391)
- Helen Zalph, Sep 6, 1981 (Cassette 138A)
- Irving Zeidman, Feb 14, 1985 (Cassette 140A - 140C, Cd OH-01-426 / OH-01-427 / OH-01-428 / OH-01-429 / OH-01-430)
- Belle Zeller, Jan 8, 1986; Jan 9, 1986; Jan 14, 1986 (Cassette 160A - 160C, Cd OH-01-191 / OH-01-192 / OH-01-193 / OH-01-194 / OH-01-195)
  Related Materials
  Zeller was interviewed by Irwin Yellowitz, a professor of labor history at the City University of New York and fellow Professional Staff Congress member. More information about Yellowitz and the Professional Staff Congress is available in the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Oral History Collection. These collections are also held by Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives; call number WAG 009 and OH 061 respectively.
- Transcripts (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5)
- Access CDs OH-01-444 to OH-01-497 (Box 21)